Privacy Policy
--------------

Our privacy policy is written to help you find out how Seafile Ltd. handles personal information. Please read our privacy policy carefully to understand how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your personal information on our website.

### What personal information do we collect?

#### seafile.com

seafile.com uses Google Analytics for site usage analysis. Only non-personally-identifying information that web browsers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request are sent to Google Analytics. The purpose of collecting such information is solely to better understand how visitors use the website. We may, from time to time, aggregate the visitor information in a statistical way to produce usage reports. Please refer to Google Analytics' [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) to get a better understanding how Google process the information.

#### Customer Center

When registering or submitting a form on our customer center, you may be asked to enter your name, your organization's name, email address, phone number or other details.

#### Seafile server and Apps

Seafile server do not send any information with regard to your usage to Seafile Ltd.. Seafile clients for Windows, Mac, and Linux regularly check seafile.com for new versions of clients. The version checking request contains a non-personally identifiable unique id, which we use for client usage statistic purpose only. This ID doesn't contain any personal information. Apps for Android and iOS don't send any information to Seafile Ltd..

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register in customer center in the following ways:

* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
* To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

### How do we protect visitor information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order and enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookies are used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.

We use cookies in two cases:

* Cookies are used to collect non-personally-identifiable information to Google Analytics.
* Cookies are used in our customer center to remember your browser and preferences. So that you can automatically login next time you visit customer center.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies settings.

If you disable cookies, some minor features might be disabled.

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

#### Community

#### About

#### Support

Copyright ©2022 Seafile Ltd.
